flemingcollege.ca 2015-06-12

# Privacy Policy : Fleming College

## Privacy Statement for Online Visitors

Fleming College is committed to protecting the privacy of our online visitors and to ensuring that you have a secure online experience. For most of our site, you are able to navigate through without providing any personal information; however, in some instances we may require some personal information in order to provide you with full services.

In these situations, the collection, use, disclosure, and retention of your personal information will be in compliance with Ontario’s Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act (FIPPA). Use of Personal Information Collected Online The primary uses of personal information collected online are: 

  1. To help you quickly find services of information on the site. 
  2. To help us create and deliver content most relevant to you.
  3. To alert you to special offers, updated information and other new services or programs.

### Control of Your Personal Information

At any time, you may choose to be removed from any mailing lists that may result from your registration on our site. Please contact us at info@flemingcollege.ca

### Cookies

To ensure that we are publishing content that our customers desire, Fleming College collects aggregated site-visitation statistics using cookies. However, we do not track individuals’ use of the site. A cookie is placed on the customer’s machine (if the customer accepts cookies) or is read if the customer has visited the site previously.

If you choose not to have your browser accept cookies from the site, you will still be able to view the text on the screen. However, you may not experience a personalized visit and some of the site features may be disabled.

Revised: December 23, 2013
  *[December 23, 2013]: 2013-12-23T09:40:07-0500
